Guide to the Arthur Levitt, Jr. Papers
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series XIII: SEC Correspondents Index
  - Kovener, Donald W. US SEC - Office of Administrative and Personnel Management, TO: Oct. 6, 1997; Nov. 24, 1999
  - Kraft, Robert New England Patriots, TO: Oct. 7, 1998
  - Kramer, Peggy US SEC, Jan. 1997
  - Krat, Gary W. Royal Alliance Associates, Inc. TO: Apr. 20, 1995
  - Krouse, James M. National Association of State Auditors, Comptrollers & Treasurers, TO: Jan. 9, 1997
  - Krumm, DiAnne, TO: Apr. 20, 1995
  - Kunin, Madeleine May US Ambassador, Switzerland, FROM: Jan. 8, 1999; TO: Jan. 20, 1999
  - Kuperberg, Martin A. US SEC - Northeast Regional Office, FROM: Jan. 31, 1996; TO: Feb. 9, 1996
  - Kurdy, Kali Borah High School, TO: May 1, 2000
  - Kwalwasser, Edward New York Stock Exchange, TO: Feb. 17, 1995; Dec. 5, 1995
  - Kulikowski, James M. US House of Representatives, TO: Dec. 11, 1995
  - Kyl, Jon US Senate, FROM: Jul. 24, 1995; Nov. 17, 1995; TO: Sep. 12, 1995; Jan. 2, 1996
  - LaFalce, John US House of Representatives, FROM: Oct. 10, 1996; May 9, 2000; TO: Mar. 16, 1995; Dec. 10, 1996; Sep. 30, 1998; May 26, 1999; Jun. 20, 2000
  - Labrecque, Thomas G. Chase Manhattan Corp. FROM: Oct. 3, 1996; TO: Oct. 18, 1996; Jan. 5, 1999
  - Laby, Arthur US SEC, TO: Aug. 26, 1997
  - Lacher, Roland Singulus Tehcnologies GmbH, Germany, TO: Apr. 25, 1997
  - Lackritz, Marc E. Securities Industry Association, FROM: Jul. 27, 1993; Dec. 14, 1995; Jan. 30, 1995; Oct. 16, 1995; May 22, 1996; Jul. 22, 1996; Jan. 30, 1997; May 30, 1997; Jun. 12, 1997; Sep. 24, 1999; TO: Aug. 25, 1993; Jan. 10, 1995; Jan. 18, 1995; Feb. 17 1995; Apr. 20, 1995; Jun. 7, 1995; Nov. 8
  - Lader, Philip US Small Business Administration; US Ambassador to UK, FROM: Jun. 16, 1995; May 12, 1999; TO: Jul. 7, 1995; Jan. 29, 1997; Jun. 7, 1999
  - Lai, Mary M. Long Island University, FROM: Aug. 2, 1995; TO: Aug. 7, 1995
  - Lake, Anthony Assistant to the President for National Security Affairs, White House, TO: [Mar. 14], 1995; Nov. 5, 1996
  - Lambert, Robert Financial Times, FROM: Feb. 10, 1998; TO: Feb. 18, 1998
  - Lambiase, Ralph A. Department of Banking, CT - Division of Securities, TO: Feb. 17, 1995; Oct. 19, 2000; TO: Apr. 21, 1995
  - Lam, Robert M. Securities Commission, PA, FROM: Mar. 10, 1995; Mar. 3, 1998; Apr. 9, 1998; TO: Mar. 27, 1995; Apr. 21, 1995; Apr. 15, 1998; Apr. 16, 1998
  - Lamm, Norman Yeshiva University, FROM: Sep. 21, 1993
  - Lanchart, Irving, TO: Apr. 20, 1995
  - Lane, Brian US SEC - Division of Corporation Finance, TO: Feb. 13, 1998; May 14, 1998
  - Lane, Neal National Science Foundation, TO: Oct. 10, 1995
  - Lang, Nancy, TO: Apr. 20, 1995
  - Lang, Robert Todd. Weil, Gotshal & Manges LLP, FROM: Feb. 14, 1995; TO: Feb. 24, 1995
  - Langevoort, Donald C. Vanderbuilt University School of Law, FROM: Mar. 25, 1997; TO: Dec. 23, 1996; Apr. 17, 1997
  - Langley, R. Warren Pacific Stock Exchange, TO: Mar. 7, 1997
  - Langner, Jay B. FROM: Jul. 13, 1995
  - Lantos, Tom US House of Representatives, FROM: Aug. 3, 1993; May 14, 1997; Jan. 5, 1998; TO: Aug. 16, 1993; Jan. 20, 1998
  - Large, Andrew Securities and Investment Board, UK; Barclays Bank PLC, UK; FROM: May 11, 1995; [May] 19, 1995; Jun. 21, 1995; Nov. 4, 1996; Dec. 20, 1996; Oct. 6, 1999; TO: May 18, 1995; May 26, 1995; Jul. 7, 1995; Sep. 19, 1996; Nov. 22, 1996; Dec. 26, 1996; Dec. 30, 1996; Sep. 28, 1999; Oct. 25, 1999
  - Largent, Steve US House of Representatives, FROM: [n.d.]; TO: Feb. 18, 1997; Mar. 5, 1997; Dec. 23, 1998
  - Larson, Peter Brunswick Corporation, TO: Feb. 19, 1999
  - Laskawy, Philip A. Ernst & Young, LLP, TO: Nov. 27, 2000
  - Lasser, Lawrence J. Putnam Investments, FROM: Aug. 30, 1999; TO: Sep. 16, 1999
  - Lateef, Noel V. Foreign Policy Association, TO: May 17, 1996
  - Lau, Mimi National Association of Securities Dealers, Inc. TO: Feb. 17, 1995
  - Lauk, Kurt J. VEBA Aktiengesellschaft, Germany, FROM: Oct. 2, 1995; TO: Oct. 10, 1995
  - Laurie, Marilyn AT&T, FROM: Feb. 28, 1997; TO: Mar. 6, 1997
  - Lausberg, Cheryl E. Senator, Republic of South Africa, TO: Mar. 7, 1995
  - Lawrence, Carmen J. US SEC - Northeast Regional Office, TO: Dec. 30, 1996
  - Lawson, Rochelle US SEC - Office of Investor Education and Assistance, TO: Mar. 29, 2000
  - Lay, Kenneth L. Enron Corporation, TO: Jun. 13, 2000
  - Lazio, Rick US House of Representatives, FROM: Apr. 24, 1998 (filed under Bliley, Jun. 5, 1998); TO: Feb. 18, 1997; Mar. 5, 1997
  - Leach, James A. US House of Representatives, FROM: Jun. 6, 1995; Jan. 2, 2001; TO: May 8, 1995 (filed under Robert Rubin, May 16, 1995); Jun. 9, 1995; May 28, 1997; Sep. 30, 1998; Jan. 29, 2001
  - Leahy, Patrick US Senate, FROM: Sep. 25, 1997; TO: Oct. 6, 1997
  - Ledes, John G. Beauty Fashion, FROM: Dec. 10, 1996
  - Ledford, Chip National Association of Securities Dealers, Inc. TO: Feb. 17, 1995
  - Lee, Barbara US House of Representatives, FROM: May 9, 2000; TO: Jun. 20, 2000
  - Lee, Bill Lann US Department of Justice, TO: Mar. 16, 2000
  - Lee, Sheila Jackson US House of Representatives, TO: Mar. 27, 1995
  - Lee, Shepard Lee Auto Malls, FROM: Dec. 5, 2000
  - Lee, Yong-Keun Financial Supervisory Commission, Korea, FROM: Apr. 11, 2000; TO: Apr. 20, 2000
  - LeFrak, Samuel J. LeFrak Organization, FROM: Sep. 7, 1993: TO: Sep. 15, 1993
  - Lehner, Daniel A. Inflight Newspapers, Inc. FROM: Aug. 25, 1993: TO: Sep. 13, 1993
  - Leichter, Franz S. State Senate, NY, FROM: Apr. 3, 1997; TO: Apr. 15, 1997
  - Leighton, Paul J. MidAmerican Energy Holdings Company, FROM: Dec. 3, 1997; TO: Dec. 11, 1997
  - Leiman, Leonard M. Fulbright & Jowarski, FROM: Oct. 20, 1997; TO: Oct. 28, 1997
  - Leisenring, James J. Financial Accounting Standards Board, FROM: Apr. 15, 1998; TO: May 4, 1998
  - Lerach, William S. Milberg Weiss Bershad Hynes & Lerach, FROM: Feb. 26, 1997; Sep. 17, 1997; TO: Mar. 13, 1997; Nov. 14, 1997
  - Lev, Baruch New York University - Leonard N. Stern School of Business, TO: Jun. 13, 2000
  - Levin, Carl US Senate, FROM: Oct. 19, 1995; Nov. 14, 2000; TO: Nov. 13, 1995; Nov. 20, 1997; Apr. 20, 1999; May 30, 2000; Dec. 12, 2000 ( Becker, David)
  - Levin, Ezra G. Kramer, Levin, Naftalis, Nessen, Kamin & Frankel, TO: Mar. 8, 1995
  - Levin, Jerry Time Warner, TO: Apr. 6, 1995
  - Levin, Wilbur A. County Clerk, Brooklyn, NY, FROM: Oct. 17, 1995;TO: Nov. 7, 1995
  - Levine, David US SEC - Division of Enforcement, TO: Oct. 14, 1999
  - Levine, Lawrence W. FROM: Jan. 12, 1995; TO: Feb. 21, 1995
  - Levine, Theodore A. Paine Webber Group, Inc. FROM: Aug. 2, 1993; TO: Aug. 9, 1993; Oct. 23 1995; Jan. 30. 1997
  - Levitt, Arthur, III, FROM: Sep. 12, 1995
  - Levitt, Frederick Packaging Products Corporation, TO: Apr. 20, 1995
  - Levitte, Jean-David Consellier Diplomatique ala Presidence, Paris, France, TO: Feb. 2, 1996
  - Lewis, Drew Union Pacific Corp. FROM: Jul. 1, 1996; TO: Jul. 16, 1996
  - Lewis, John US House of Representatives, FROM: Oct. 10, 1996; Nov. 20, 1997;TO: Dec. 10, 1996; Jan. 20, 1998
  - Lewis, Loida Nicholas TLC Beatrice Holdings International, Inc. TO: Dec. 23, 1998
  - Lewis, Wilma US Attorney, TO: Nov. 12, 1998 (RE: Zarb, Frank)
  - Lewis, William M., Jr. Morgan Stanley Dean Witter, TO: Oct. 15, 1999
  - Li, Laurence Securities and Futures Commission, Hong Kong, TO: Aug. 9, 2000
  - Liang, Paul PBS Partners, LLC, FROM: Aug. 10, 1999; TO: Sep. 2, 1999
  - Liberman, Joseph I. US Senate, FROM: Mar. 21, 2000; TO: Mar. 31, 2000
  - Lichtenberger, Vincent US SEC - Southeast Regional Office, TO: Apr. 15, 1996
  - Liebenberg, Christopher Minister of Finance, Republic of South Africa, TO: Mar. 7, 1995
  - Lieberman, Joseph I. US Senate, FROM: Nov. 19, 1996; TO: Dec. 18, 1996; Nov. 20, 1997
  - Liftin, John M. Kidder, Peabody & Co. FROM: Jul. 25, 1996; TO: Aug. 21, 1996; Aug. 29, 1997
  - Liman, Lewis J. Assistant US Attorney, FROM: Jul. 2, 1998
  - Limber, Trudy, TO: Apr. 20, 1995
  - Lin, S. D. Taiwan Stock Exchange Corp., Taipei, TO: Aug. 8, 1995
  - Lin, Tzong-Yeong Securities and Futures Commission, Taiwan, TO: Sep. 23, 1998
  - Linden, Derek National Association of Securities Dealers, Inc. TO: Feb. 17, 1995
  - Lindros, Carl Santa Barbara Securities, TO: Apr. 20, 1995
  - Lindsay, Richard R. US SEC - Division of Market Regulation, TO: Feb. 13, 1998; Mar. 10, 1998; Aug. 31, 1998
  - Linnehan, John National Association of Securities Dealers, Inc. TO: Feb. 17, 1995
  - Linowitz, Sol. M. FROM: Aug. 9, 1993; TO: Aug. 24, 1993
  - Linsmeier, Thomas J. American Accounting Association, FROM: Apr. 10, 1998; TO: Apr. 30, 1998
  - Linton, Robert E. Leslie/Linton Entertainment, FROM: Jul. 27, 2000; TO: Aug. 15, 2000; Aug. 21, 2000
  - Lipe, Robert C. University of Oklahoma, OK - School of Accounting, FROM: Apr. 30, 1998; TO: Jun. 5, 1998
  - Lipinski, William O. US House of Representatives, FROM: Oct. 10, 1996; TO: Dec. 10, 1996
  - Lipner, Kenneth, FROM: Jun. 13, 2000; TO: Jul. 17, 2000
  - Lipper, A. Michael Lipper Analytical Services, FROM: Dec. 31, 1994; Sep. 25, 1997; TO: Jan. 19; 1995; Oct. 3, 1997
  - Lipper, Kenneth, FROM: Jan. 29, 1999; TO: Feb. 25, 1999; Jun. 22, 1999
  - Lipton, Martin Wachtell, Lipton, Rosen & Katz, TO: Oct. 23, 1995; Mar. 6, 1996
  - Lister, Steven American Stock Exchange, TO: Dec. 5, 1995
  - Litan, Robert Brookings Institution, TO: Aug. 16, 1999; Oct. 14, 1999
  - Littrell, Romie F. Shen Da University, People's Republic of China, FROM: Nov. 30, 1995; TO: Jan. 2, 1996
  - Livingston, Philip B. Financial Executives Institute, FROM: May 20, 1999; TO: Jun. 4, 1999
  - Livingston, Robert US House of Representatives, TO: Feb. 17, 1995; Nov. 15, 1995; Jan. 3, 1996; Jan. 19, 1996; Feb. 9, 1996; Oct. 2, 1996; Mar. 13, 1998; Jul. 20, 1998; Jan. 4, 1999
  - Liu, Hong China Securities Regulatory Commission, People's Republic of China, FROM: Aug. 26, 1997 (filed under Zhou, Zhengqing, Sep. 26, 1997)); Nov. 27, 1997 (filed under Zhou, Zhengqing, Dec. 5, 1997)
  - Livingston, Homer J. Chicago Stock Exchange, FROM: Aug. 3, 1993; TO: Aug. 9, 1993; Jan. 12, 1995; Feb. 17, 1995
  - Livingston, Lennard L. TO: Apr. 20, 1995
  - Lloyd, Emily Columbia University, FROM: Sep. 2, 1997
  - Lochner, Philip R., Jr. FROM: Jan. 31, 1996; Feb. 1, 1996; May 28, 1997; Sep. 23, 1999; TO: Feb. 8, 1996; Mar. 6, 1996; Jun. 27, 1997; Oct. 25, 1999
  - Loeb, Peter K. FROM: Dec. 16, 1996; TO: Jan. 22, 1997
  - Lofgren, Zoe US House of Representatives, FROM: Oct. 10, 1996; TO: Dec. 10, 1996
  - Logson, Neva S. TO: Apr. 20, 1995
  - Logue, Dennis E. Dartmouth College, TO: Apr. 26, 1995
  - Long, Clay Long, Aldridge & Norman, TO: Mar. 7, 1997 (RE: Arms, Abbie)
  - Long, G. US SEC, FROM: Mar. 31, 1994 (Morrow, C. -personal file)
  - Long, Ronald C. US SEC - Philadelphia Office, TO: Dec. [17], 1997; Sep. 8, 2000
  - Longstaff, John L. Institute for Sertified Financial Planners, FROM: Mar. 13, 1996; TO: Mar. 29, 1996
  - Longstreth, Bevis Debevoise & Plimpton, TO: Nov. 27, 2000
  - Lopez, Ivette US SEC - Division of Market Regulation, TO: Feb. 17 1995
  - Lorlo, Rene Walnut Street Securities, TO: Apr. 20, 1995
  - Lorne, Simon M. Salomon Brothers, Inc. FROM: Jan. 31, 1997; TO: May 11, 1995; Feb. 26, 1997; Aug. 29, 1997
  - Loss, Louis Harvard University - School of Law, FROM: mar. 16, 1995; TO: Jan. 27, 1995; Apr. 18, 1995
  - Lott, Trent US Senate, FROM: Aug. 8, 1995; TO: Aug. 29, 1995
  - Lovejoy, Thomas Smithsonian Institution, TO: Oct. 19, 1995
  - Lowenstein, Louis Columbia University, FROM: May 1, 1996; Nov. 24, 1998; TO: Mar. 6, 1996; May 14, 1996; May 27, 1997(Balamaci, N.); Dec. 1, 1998
  - Lowenstein, Roger, FROM: May 1, 1995; TO: May 16, 1995
  - Lowey, Nita W. US House of Representatives, FROM: Apr. 27, 1995; TO: May 12, 1995
  - Lubner, Bertie Plate Glass and Shatterprufe Industries, Ltd.; Republic of South Africa, TO: Mar. 7, 1995
  - Luccock, Phillip H. Institute for Sertified Financial Planners, TO: May 14, 1998
  - Ludwig, Eugene A. Comptroller of the Currency; Bankers Trust; Promontory Financial Group, FROM: Mar. 16, 1998; Sep. 3, 1999; TO: Dec. 5, 1997; Apr. 6, 1998; Sep. 14, 1999; Jan. 29, 2001
  - Luecke, Richard Harvard University - Graduate School of Business Administration, TO: May 1, 1995
  - Lugar, Richard G. US Senate, FROM: Dec. 17, 1999; TO: Jul. 25, 1997; Mar. 2, 2000
  - Luikart, John F. Sutro & Co. FROM: Mar. 5, 1996; TO: Mar. 19, 1996
  - Lundquist, Oliver, FROM: Dec. 1, 1998; TO: [Dec. 1], 1998
  - Lupberger, Edwin Entergy Corporation, TO: Dec. 5, 1997
  - Lupia, Terry A. Securities Commission, PA, TO: Apr. 20, 1995
  - Lutz, William D. Rutgers - State University of NJ, TO: Jun. 22, 1995; Aug. 21, 1996
  - Lyman, Princeton N. US Embassy, Republic of South Africa, TO: [Mar. 14], 1995
  - Lynch, Brian J. Morgan, Lewis & Bockius, LLP. TO: Dec. 20, 1996; Dec. 23, 1996
  - Lynch, Gary Davis Polk & Warwell, TO: Mar. 5, 1998
  - Lynch, Peter, TO: Apr. 20, 1995; May 2, 1996
  - Lyons, James E. FROM: Aug. 17, 1993: TO: Sep. 13, 1993
  - Lyons, William M. American Century Investments, TO: Apr. 17, 1998
  - Macaleer, James R. Shared Medical Systems, TO: Sep. 30, 1997
  - Macedo, Augusto, TO: Jan. 30, 1995
  - Machold, Roland M. New Jersey Department of Treasury, Division of Investment, FROM: Mar. 14, 1995 (encl. To Drysdale, Apr. 11, 1995); TO: May 1, 1995
  - Mack, Connie US Senate, FROM: Jun. 24, 1996; Dec. 7, 2000; TO: Jan. 30, 1995; Apr. 19, 1996; Jul. 18, 1996; Jan. 29, 2001
  - Macklin, Gordon S. FROM: Aug. 2, 1993; TO: Aug. 9, 1993
  - MacLaury, Bruce K. TO: Mar. 16, 1999
  - Maco, Paul S. US SEC - Office of Municipal Securities, FROM: Aug. 25, 1995 (Richard Baker); Jun. 22, 1999; TO: Aug. 4, 1995; May 27, 1999 (Mires, Charles D.)
  - Madden, Joe, Jr. Securities Department, AR, TO: Apr. 21, 1995
  - Maddux, Dan American Payroll Association, TO: Aug. 23, 1999
  - Madoff, Andrew H. Bernard L. Madoff Investment Securities, FROM: Feb. 12 1995; TO: Feb. 20, 1996
  - Madoff, Bernard L. Bernard L. Madoff Investment Securities, FROM: Jan. 5, 1995; TO: Jan. 19, 1995; Dec. 19, 1995; Dec. 13, 1996
  - Madoff, Peter B. Bernard L. Madoff Investment Securities, FROM: Jan. 5, 1995; Jan. [12], 1996; Apr. 3, 1998; TO: Jan. 19, 1995; Jan. 29, 1996; Apr. 6, 1998
  - Madonna, Jon C. KPMG Peat Marwick, FROM: Nov. 21, 1995; Dec. 19, 1995; TO: Dec. 7, 1995; Jan. 2, 1996
  - Maguire, Thomas P. International Union of Operating Engineers, FROM: Sep. 6, 1996; TO: Sep. 30, 1996
  - Maher, John A. Securities Commission, PA, FROM: Mar. 3, 1998; TO: Apr. 16, 1998
  - Mahmud, Hasan Zein Jakarta Stock Exchange, Indonesia, TO: May 5, 1995
  - Mahoney, Edward M. Fortis Investors Inc. TO: Apr. 20, 1995
  - Mai, Vincent A. AEA Investors, Inc. TO: Jan. 29, 2001
  - Majid, Mohamed Munir Bin Abdul Securities Commission, Malaysia; IOSCO, TO: Mar. 22, 1995; May 5, 1995; Oct. 22, 1997; Sep. 10, 1998; Jun. 9, 1999
  - Makens, Hugh Warner, Norcross & Judd, TO: Oct. 23 1995
  - Malamud, Carl Internet Multicasting Service, TO: Oct. 10, 1995
  - Malkin, Peter L. Wien & Malkin, LLP, FROM: Nov. 18, 1997; TO: Nov. 24, 1997
  - Malmenstam-Skytt, Birgit Swedish Shareholders Association, Sweden, TO: Jun. 25, 1999
  - Malone, Joseph Equitable Life Assurance Society, TO: Mar 2, 1995; Apr. 20, 1995; Jun. 7, 1995
  - Maloney, Carolyn B. US House of Representatives, FROM: Apr. 27, 1995; Mar. 26, 1997;TO: May 12, 1995; Apr. 25, 1997
  - Maloney, Robert H. Northwestern Mutual Life/Baird, TO: Apr. 20, 1995
  - Malphrus, Stephen R. Financial Sector Group, FROM: Sep. 22, 1999; TO: Oct. 7, 1999
  - Mandell, Robert US SEC - Division of Corporation Finance, TO: Oct. 11, 1995
  - Mann, Michael D. US SEC - Office of International Affairs, FROM: Feb. 22, 1995; Jan. 12, 1995 (Re: Iglesias); Mar. 6, 1995 (Re: Tyson); Apr. 17, 1997 (Re: Shin); Sep. 25, 1996
  - Manning, Bayless Paul, Weiss, Rifkind, Wharton & Garrison; Manning Companies, FROM: Oct. 28, 1998(RE: Hoyl, Geoff);TO: Jan. 4, 1995; Jan. 3, 1996; Dec. 9, 1996; Jan. 5, 1998; Oct. 30, 1998; [Dec. 29], 1998
  - Manton, Thomas J. US House of Representatives, FROM: Apr. 27, 1995; Oct. 10, 1996; Feb. 27, 1997; Mar. 10, 1997(Giamo, Jennifer); Apr. 11, 1997; May 23, 1997 (filed under Buffet, Warren, Aug. 25, 1997); May 27, 1997; Jun. 12, 1997; TO: May 12, 1995; Dec. 10, 1996; Mar. 5, 1997; Mar. 14, 1997; Mar. 21
  - Marcelino, Juan Marcel US SEC - Boston District Office, TO: Dec. 30, 1996
  - Marcereon, Kenneth T. US SEC, TO: May 7, 1996
  - Marcus, Gill Joint Standing Committee of Finance, Republic of South Africa, FROM: Mar. 8, 1995; C65TO: Mar. 7, 1995; Mar. 22, 1995
  - Markels, Michael VERSAR, Inc. FROM: Jul. 30, 1993; TO: Aug. 4, 1993
  - Markese, John American Association of Individual Investors, FROM: Oct. 6, 1999; TO: Apr. 14, 1998; Mar. 16, 1999; Oct. 14, 1999
  - Markey, Edward J. US House of Representatives, FROM: Mar. 13, 1995; Nov. 21, 1995; Mar. 26, 1996; Apr. 9, 1996; Jun. 12, 1996; Dec. 16, 1996; Feb. 3, 1997; Mar. 19, 1997; Apr. 28, 1997; May 23, 1997 (filed under Buffet, Warren, Aug. 25, 1997); Jul. 11, 1997; Sep. 12, 1997; Mar. 3, 1998; May 20, 1998
  - Marks, Arthur J. New Enterprise Associates, FROM: Mar. 22, 1995; TO: May 1, 1995
  - Marquingny, Rebecca US SEC - Office of Equal Employment Opportunity, TO: Mar.30, 1999
  - Marron, Donald B. PaineWebber, Inc. TO: Feb. 17, 1995; Mar 2, 1995; Mar. 27, 1995; Apr. 20, 1995; Jun. 7, 1995; Jan. 30. 1997; Oct. 17, 1997; Oct. 23, 1997; Apr. 8, 1998; Nov. 23, 1998; Jan. 29, 2001
  - Marshall, Capricia Penavic White House - Social Secretary, FROM: Apr. 8, 1999 (RE: Clinton, William J.)
  - Marshall, Thurgood, Jr. White House - Cabinet Affairs Secretary, TO: May 27, 1998
  - Martel, Jean Commission des Valeurs Mobilieres du Quebec, Canada, FROM: Feb. 27, 1996; TO: Mar. 14, 1996; Dec. 26, 1996
  - Martin, Michael Equico Securities, Inc. TO: Mar 2, 1995; Apr. 20, 1995
  - Masanz, Timothy J. National Governors' Association, TO: Jan. 9, 1997
  - Mason, Eli Mason & Company, LLP; AICPA; FROM: Jun. 6, 1996; Jul. 1, 1997; Oct. 27, 1997; Jan. 8, 1998; Jun. 21, 2000 (Schumer, Charles E.); TO: Jul. 3, 1996; Aug. 29, 1997; Dec. 5, 1997; Jan. 30, 1998
  - Mason, Raymond A. Legg Mason, Inc. TO: May 1, 1995; Jun. 7, 1995; Dec. 10, 1997
  - Masterson, Michael M. Washington Square Securities, Inc. TO: Apr. 20, 1995
  - Mathias, Edward Carlyle Group, FROM: Feb. 9, 1996; TO: Mar. 11, 1996
  - Mathisen, Tyler, FROM: Apr. 10, 1998
  - Matthews, Betty Consumer Credit Counseling Service, TO: May 14, 1998
  - Mattimore, John US SEC - Southeast Regional Office, TO: Apr. 15, 1996
  - Mathur, Colette World Economic Forum, FROM: Sep. 18, 1997; TO: Nov. 20, 1997
  - Maughan, Deryck C. Salomon Brothers, Inc.; Citigroup, TO: Feb. 17, 1995; Mar 2, 1995; Mar. 27, 1995; Apr. 20, 1995; Jun. 7, 1995; Nov. 6, 1996; Jan. 30. 1997; Apr. 10, 1997; Aug. 15, 1997; Oct. 17, 1997; Apr. 8, 1998; Jan. 29, 2001
  - May, S. Beville, FROM: Feb. 26, 1996
  - Mayer, Martin Brookings Institution, FROM: Nov. 1, [1994];TO: Jan. 11, 1995; Sep. 14, 1998
  - Mazur, Francois I. US SEC - Division of Market Regulation, TO: Feb. 17 1995
  - McAlevey, Mike, TO: Jan. 10, 2001
  - McAuliffe, Frank National Association of Securities Dealers, Inc. TO: Feb. 17, 1995
  - McCabe, Mrs. TO: [n.d.]
  - McCall, H. Carl State Comptroller, NY, FROM: Aug. 3, 1993; Dec. 23, 1997; Jan. 28, 1998; Apr. 7, 1998; Feb. 18, 1999; TO: Aug. 18, 1993; Jan. 21, 1998; Mar. 4, 1998; Apr. 15, 1998; Mar. 15, 1999
  - McCall, James H. California Capital Access Forum, CA, FROM: Oct. 17, 1995; TO: Nov. 8, 1995
  - McCarrick, Theodore E. Archbishop of Washington, TO: Jan. 23, 2001
  - McCarthy, Carolyn US House of Representatives, FROM: Jan. 20, 2000; TO: May 19, 2000
  - McCaul, Elizabeth Banking Department, NY, FROM: Mar. 15, 2000; TO: Apr. 24, 2000
  - McClellan, Kenneth Department of Commerce and Insurance, TN, TO: Apr. 21, 1995
  - McCollum, Bill US House of Representatives, FROM: May 27, 1997; TO: May 29, 1997
  - McConnaughey, Robert S. American Counsel of Life Insurance, FROM: Oct. 31 1995; TO: Nov. 8, 1995
  - McConnell, James M. US SEC - Executive Director, FROM: Dec. 27, 1995; Aug. 26, 1998; TO: Oct. 4, 1995
  - McCracken, Paul W. University of Michigan, MI - School of Business, FROM: Oct. 21, 1996; TO: Nov. 4, 1996
  - McCreery, William G. FROM: Aug. 14, 2000; TO: Aug. 24, 2000
  - McCullough, Brian US House of Representatives, TO: Mar. 5, 1997
  - McDonald, Alonzo L. TO: Dec. 7, 1998
  - McDonald, Robert Office of the Attorney General, TO: Apr. 21, 1995
  - McDonough, Gerald C. TO: Mar. 16, 1999
  - McDonough, William J. Federal Reserve Bank of New York, TO: Jan. 29, 2001
  - McEldowney, Kenneth Consumer Action, FROM: Aug. 1, 2000; TO: Sep. 7, 2000
  - McElroy, John L. Wheat, First Securities, Inc. TO: Mar 2, 1995; Apr. 20, 1995
  - McEvoy, John National Council of State Housing Agencies, TO: Jan. 9, 1997
  - McGovern, Lore Harp, FROM: Apr. 13, 1999; TO: May 5, 1999
  - McInerney, Alice Bureau of Investor Protection, TO: Apr. 21, 1995
  - McIntyre, Mildred J. FROM: Jul. 21, 1995
  - McInerney, Tom Welsh Carson Anderson & Stowe, TO: Aug. 16, 1999
  - McIntosh, David M. US House of Representatives, FROM: Apr. 7, 1995; Mar. 28, 1996; Apr. 11, 1996; Dec. 11, 1996; Jan. 12, 1998; Aug. 3, 1999; TO: May 18, 1995; Aug. 10, 1995; Apr. 2, 1996; Apr. 22, 1996; Dec. 11, 1996; Mar. 19, 1997 (Walker, Richard); Apr. 9, 1997; Jul. 15, 1997 (Glassman, James); J
  - McKinney, Cynthia Ann US House of Representatives, FROM: Oct. 10, 1996; TO: Dec. 10, 1996
  - McLagan, Bruce McLagan Partners Inc. TO: Apr. 26, 1995
  - McLaughlin, Joseph Brown & Wood, FROM: May 5, 1995; Dec. 20, 1996; Jan. 17, 1997; TO: May 22, 1995; Feb. 4, 1997
  - McLaughlin, Joseph T. Credit Suisse First Boston Corp. FROM: Aug. 14, 1997; TO: Aug. 26, 1997
  - McLoughlin, Philip W.S. Griffith & Co, Inc. TO: Apr. 20, 1995
  - McLucas, William US SEC - Division of Enforcement, TO: Mar. 10, 1998; Aug. 3, 1998; Mar. 20, 2000
  - McMichael, Kathy National School Boards Association, TO: Jan. 9, 1997
  - McNees, Donald Towers Perrin, TO: May 1, 1995
  - McNeill, Corbin A., Jr. PECO Energy Company, TO: Dec. 5, 1997
  - McPhearson, D. Richard Nationwide Financial Services, Inc. TO: Apr. 20, 1995
  - McWhinney, Madeline H. Dale, Elliott & Co. FROM: Sep. 30, 1998; TO: Oct. 9 1998
  - Meade, Dana G. Tenneco, Inc. FROM: Dec. 22, 1999; TO: Sep. 9, 1998; [Dec. 9], 1998; Dec. 23, 1998; Jan. 11, 1999; Apr. 30, 1999
  - Mebane, G. Allen UNIFI Corporation, FROM: Aug. 21, 1996; TO: Sep. 13, 1996
  - Mecum, Dudley C. FROM: Aug. 17, 1993: TO: Aug. 25, 1993
  - Meehan, Martin T. US House of Representatives, FROM: Jul. 9, 1997; TO: Aug. 1, 1997; Nov. 14, 1997
  - Meek, Carrie US House of Representatives, FROM: Nov. 20, 1997; TO: Jan. 20, 1998
  - Mehta, D. R. Securities and Exchange Board, India, FROM: Feb. 28, 1998 (see Kar, Pratip); Aug.30, 1995; Apr. 4, 1996; Nov. 28, 1996; TO: Mar. 13, 1995; Nov. 8, 1995; Mar. 6, 1996; Apr. 11, 1996; Dec. 11, 1996; [Nov.]. 1999; Jan. 24, 2001
  - Melvin, Christopher Melvin Securities, FROM: Aug. 1, 1997; TO: Sep. 17, 1997
  - Mendell, Oliver M. Chase Manhattan Bank, FROM: Mar. 9, 1998; TO: Mar. 16, 1998
  - Mendoza. Gary Department of Corporations, CA (Commissioner), TO: Apr. 21, 1995
  - Meier, Henri B. F. Hoffman-La Roche AG, Switzerland, FROM: Feb. 21, 1996; TO: Feb. 27, 1996
  - Melamed, Leo Chicago Mercantile Exchange, FROM: Feb. 18, 1997; TO: Mar. 4, 1997
  - Melancon, Barry C. American Institute of Certified Public Accountants, FROM: Jan. 5, 1996; May 12, 1998; TO: Jan. 29, 1996; Jun. 10, 1998; Nov. 27, 2000
  - Melican, James P. International Paper, FROM: Feb. 14, 1995; TO: Mar. 17, 1995
  - Menezes, Victor Salomon Smith Barney Holdings Inc. TO: Aug. 4, 1999
  - Meridor, Dan Ministry of Finance, Israel, TO: Apr. 25, 1997
  - Messenger, James H. National Financial Services Corporation, TO: Oct. 23, 1997